David

Rodriguez V.

https://drod.design heeeydavidrodriguez@gmail.com (+34) 626 854 494

Started originally as a graphic designer, but I switched from paper into screens in 2013. I am a Digital Designer focused on mobile apps with also some experience designing (and coding too) responsive websites.

According to my experience I am fortunate to had been working in so many different projects, including TV and cars, and for different kind of companies too (from startups to big ones). In a startup environment I learnt how to be a proactive and multitasking person. On the other hand, working for big companies has helped me face against complex problems like scaling a design system, or create, "defend" and maintain a set of components for a huge new product.

EDUCATION

Master in Online Marketing & Communication

IMF Business School / Universidad Camilo José Cela 2015 - 2016

Master in Web Design

BAU Centre Universitari de Disseny 2014 - 2015

Undergraduate Degree in Graphic Design

Escola d'Art i Disseny de Tarragona (EADT) 2012 - 2015

Artistic "Bachillerato"

IES Narcis Oller 2012 - 2014



Carrer de Provença, 198 08036 Barcelona (Spain)

EXPERIENCE

Movetia

UX/UI Designer Feb 2017 - Current

SEAT

UI/UX Designer May 2017 - Oct 2016

MobileJazz

UI/UX Designer Feb 2016 - May 2016

Lafosca

Junior UI Designer Jun 2015 - Jan 2016

LANGUAGES

English

B2.1

Professional working proficiency

Spanish

Native or bilingual

Catalan

Native or bilingual

Some examples of my work

LAFOSCA

SmartCitizen

Smart Citizen is a platform to generate participatory processes of people in the cities. It consists on sensors which everyone can buy and it collects an amount of data like air pollution, humidity, ... Then you can see and compare this information on the web.

Notegraphy

Notegraphy lets you write and publish everything you want to share with added style, everything you write and share will look just beautiful. It has more than 40 templates made by some of the world's best graphic designers.

FAB11

Android app design for the International Fab Lab Conference. The official app of the FAB11 - The 11th International Fab Lab Conference and Fab Festival. Being held in Boston, August 3rd-9th, 2015.

MOBILEJAZZ

Medtronic

Design and development of the website of this medical company with a worldwide recognition. We were defining their page destined to Europe, since the services provided varied according to the geographical situation.

elAbogado

Useful application to find a lawyer according to the needs of the user, with a ranking and rating system to know if the lawyer you choose is the one that best corresponds to you.

SEAT

Kombi

This is how they called the project in which I was working, although it was not his definitive name. It is a new screen design destined to a future brand's cars where the user will be able to see or handle all the information of the vehicle, improving their current system called Full Link.

MOVETIA

CaixaBank App

App restyling for one of the biggest spanish banks. We were a team of three designers who built a new design system that the company has started to implement in its main app. We worked closely with project managers and the QA team to make sure that all the work was perfectly implemented.

MORE INFO

Linkedin

David Rodriguez Valencia

Dribbble

Drod